[
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Маразм",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "915184813522505728",
        "text": "Маразм крепчалpic.twitter.com/tqhdHePcsc"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Телеканал",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Russia",
                "tag": "GSP"
            }
        ],
        "id": "914866807449772032",
        "text": "Телеканал Russia Today может прекратить вещание в США из-за давления Вашингтона.\n\nИ среди этих умалишенных мы живем"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Теперь",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "914821341169307655",
        "text": "Теперь представьте как Соловьев будучи в своем поместье нажмет геолокацию на телефоне и его лицо собственноpic.twitter.com/IpzNCqJ9YQ"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Нельзя",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "914391300010647553",
        "text": "-Мам, хочу поиграть!\n- Нельзя сына, ты не здоровый, высокий и сильный голубоглазый ариец. Ты больной и маленький.pic.twitter.com/lgNOiKJJFA"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Герман",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Греф",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Зато",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913788177751699456",
        "text": "Герман Греф забыл, что идёт прямая трансляция.\n\nЗато не врет и все честно...pic.twitter.com/7l6H4Q6RZL"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "НижнемНовгороде",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913762369570004993",
        "text": "Суд в Нижнем Новгороде запретил статью о создании динамика, спутав его с динамитом\n\nНу собственно, все что нужно знать про судебную системуpic.twitter.com/KL8CuKRlXk"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Россия",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913740943181979648",
        "text": "Россия стала лидером по темпу роста числа долларовых миллионеров \n\nА по темпу роста числа бедных?"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Сотрудника",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "ГИБДДЧелябинска",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Денег",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Пошел",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913708793082589185",
        "text": "Сотрудника ГИБДД Челябинска задержали за создание нарколаборатории. \"Во все тяжкие\" пересмотрел, это понятно.\n\nДенег нет. Пошел в бизнес."
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Урале",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "АндрейМерзляков",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913421899975266304",
        "text": "На Урале депутат Андрей Мерзляков установил видеокамеру в туалете, чтобы подглядывать за женщинами\n\nНародный избранник,которого мы заслужилиpic.twitter.com/19wO20yIy5"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Навальный",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Если",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913395045407105024",
        "text": "7 октября Навальный @navalny проведет встречу с жителями Петербурга. Если вы оттуда, то пойдете? Как относитесь к месту проведения?"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Путин",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "АфрикиА",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913371145180770304",
        "text": "Путин заявил о списании более $20 млрд долга стран Африки\n\nА если ты, дорогой россиянин, не заплатишь за свет или отопление,то тебя\nвыселят"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Минздрав",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913343925099917312",
        "text": "Минздрав опять разрешил покупать «Боярышник» без ограничений\n\nК предстоящим выборам окончательно убить клетки мозга у населения...pic.twitter.com/F2aoKUzYHe"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Урале",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Готовы",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913026061503549440",
        "text": "На Урале детей вместо уроков заставляли достраивать стадион.\n\nГотовы к Чемпионату мира по футболу 2018!!!pic.twitter.com/hSGLtHlm3j"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Рязанцы",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913000031996846080",
        "text": "Рязанцы разобрали просроченные продукты из отходов «Пятерочки»\n\nчто там про МРОТ?pic.twitter.com/A8GFEsAGai"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Очередной",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "912975770238189568",
        "text": "Очередной тебе мат, Нэвэльный.pic.twitter.com/D4vU7RUama"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Москве",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Думаю",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "ФСБ",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "912595973729390592",
        "text": "В Москве мерседес с номерами «АМР» и мигалкой насмерть сбил сотрудника ГИБДД на Новом Арбате.\n\nДумаю скажут суицид. Из ФСБ все можно!pic.twitter.com/wrDvZYapFK"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "BlackHistoryMonth",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "694656302534930432",
        "text": "Because not all of our heroes are from the past\n#BlackLivesMatter\n#BlackHistoryMonth pic.twitter.com/BaZtctibpb"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "TrayvonMartin",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695680898105212928",
        "text": "If #TrayvonMartin was white, he'd be alive today. pic.twitter.com/uXvFtJHwCh"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "BlackTwitter",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695623657410977792",
        "text": "#BlackTwitter pic.twitter.com/7hqbJ2nC7G"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "WhiteHouse",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695622271608733696",
        "text": "#Obama #WhiteHouse pic.twitter.com/mzr9AijfiA"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Happy",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Rest",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Peace",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "TrayvonMartin",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BlackHistoryMonth",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695619583995219970",
        "text": "Happy Birthday and Rest In Peace #TrayvonMartin #BlackHistoryMonth #BlackLivesMatter pic.twitter.com/LvlbNPjhmh"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "BlackSquadUS",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "ASAP",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695610990747115520",
        "text": "@BlackSquadUS @LeftWithNothin1 we need to destroy and rebuild this system ASAP"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "NYPDCop",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "FellowCopsFalselyArrested",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BeatHim",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695594310478204929",
        "text": "#NYPD Cop Wins $15M After Fellow Cops Falsely Arrested & Beat Him at His Daughter’s BDay http://goo.gl/P2dccx  pic.twitter.com/rvGonoRvfV"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Happy",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BlackHistoryMonth2016",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BlackHistory",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695592909526192128",
        "text": "Happy Birthday @HenryLouisAaron! Keep Swinging! #BlackHistoryMonth2016 #BlackHistory pic.twitter.com/qTeEgbDTGM"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Bernie",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "DemDebate",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BernieSanders",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Bernie",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695443590009389058",
        "text": "Go Bernie! #DemDebate #BernieSanders #Bernie pic.twitter.com/3r34FPfFpv"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Bronx",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "MelroseHouses",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695442582361341952",
        "text": "#2NYPD officers shot in the #Bronx Thursday evening at about 8 p.m. in the #Melrose Houses pic.twitter.com/XQbKlDufBi"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "RIPMauriceWhite",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "EarthWindAndFire",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695442116390957056",
        "text": "The world lost another legend today.#RIPMauriceWhite #EarthWindAndFire pic.twitter.com/uVESYLX7W8"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "RosaParks",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695393692463472640",
        "text": "#RosaParks chose dignity over safety&convenience.She sat down in defiance so we might stand up.God rest her soul. pic.twitter.com/HSqIZIvvtu"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "NYPD",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Queens",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695393227331883008",
        "text": "Off-duty #NYPD #cop busted for hitting 13-year-old with car in #Queens, leaving scene http://goo.gl/78m4ZW  pic.twitter.com/93Vmf2i0xz"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "NYPD",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "WhoseJob",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BustProstitutes",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Massive",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695391347809751040",
        "text": "#NYPD #Cop, Whose Job was to Bust Prostitutes, Exposed as a Pimp in Massive Sex Trafficking \nhttp://goo.gl/UwjDf1  pic.twitter.com/7QFFDWYFK1"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "HerStomach",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "FalseArrest",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "CausingMiscarriage",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695390630747328512",
        "text": "4 Cops Beat Pregnant Woman, Stomping on Her Stomach During False Arrest, Causing Miscarriage #StatenIsland, #NY\nhttp://goo.gl/IbAJYo "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Bernie2016",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "695385880958148609",
        "text": "Where the candidates stand on the issues that matter. #Bernie2016 pic.twitter.com/jb5lpjorg7"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Ferguson",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "631148910627569666",
        "text": "#FergusonRemembers If #Ferguson protestors showed up with assault rifles out it'd be an all-out GD war"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Nagasaki",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "630417600686747648",
        "text": "#Nagasaki pic.twitter.com/CG8Uk7hFtU"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Mexican",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Congress",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "628907647442550784",
        "text": "#NationalUnderwearDay\nWhen the argument in Mexican Congress is too hot pic.twitter.com/7TjxBsRa1y"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "THE",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "DARK",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "627015174210330624",
        "text": "\"IM NOT SCARED OF THE DARK\" during the day, at night, I am a little more open-minded pic.twitter.com/QILKQMoBUQ"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Life",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "622664814217830400",
        "text": "Life is a boomerang. What you give, you get. #quote #true"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Men",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "622664793267249152",
        "text": "Men must do as they may, not as they would"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "RAP",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "622664772224450560",
        "text": "Sweating on the floor when you come to see me #RAP"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Had",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "622664646835761152",
        "text": "Had to tell your moms and sister to cool it (oh-hooo!) #love #rap"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Happy",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "SuperBowl",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "561931644785811457",
        "text": "Happy Super Bowl Sunday \n#superbowlfood pic.twitter.com/s6rwMtdLom"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Bacon",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "561917739108155392",
        "text": "Making the award-winning Pigs in a Pillow again today! Bacon, goat cheese, jam, glazed donut as bread. #superbowlfood pic.twitter.com/19IWyMWGcf"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "SampledOne",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "SuperBowlFood",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "561922993870217216",
        "text": "All done making the tortilla roll ups. They're not perfect, but they taste good. #SampledOne #SuperBowlFood pic.twitter.com/gXBZ6savMM"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "FRUIT",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "561923181146300419",
        "text": "FRUIT RAINBOW- a fun way to serve your fruit today! #superbowlfood pic.twitter.com/6zzeaMQUrX"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Happy",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "SuperBowl",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "561930665294565376",
        "text": "Happy Super Bowl Sunday \n#superbowlfood pic.twitter.com/wE0W9xi3YN"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Happy",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "SuperBowl",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "561930595933384704",
        "text": "Happy Super Bowl Sunday \n#superbowlfood pic.twitter.com/nCuZVdrmiP"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Happy",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "SuperBowl",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "561930490404687872",
        "text": "Happy Super Bowl Sunday \n#superbowlfood pic.twitter.com/Qx0wTBYmBc"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Happy",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "SuperBowl",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "561930433810952192",
        "text": "Happy Super Bowl Sunday \n#superbowlfood pic.twitter.com/hTfFKhDb0M"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Mini",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Japan",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "560495579080716291",
        "text": "Mini pineapples in #Japan pic.twitter.com/pPvBz74MVn"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Ricotta",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "560495360494546944",
        "text": "Ricotta cheesecake topped with blueberries #yummy pic.twitter.com/dTNcY8LlpA"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "SinceWeBeingHonest",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "560338650819747840",
        "text": "#SinceWeBeingHonest pizza is my best friend pic.twitter.com/F6pMrPl4LN"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Scandal",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "511013584235941888",
        "text": "Scandal is gossip made tedious by morality."
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Drink",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510982641970348032",
        "text": "Drink no longer water, but use a little wine for thy stomach's sake."
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "ChemicalAccidentLouisiana",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510253529085128705",
        "text": "Hands off! It’s sacred!  Oh gosh I’m so excited! Oh no, wait I don’t give a shit! #ChemicalAccidentLouisiana"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Centerville",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510252927769141248",
        "text": "A powerful explosion heard from miles away happened at a chemical plant in Centerville, Louisiana #ColumbianChemicals"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Okay",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Good",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "DeadHorse",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510244606207070208",
        "text": "Okay. Clear. Sanation/recovery/reorganization. Good point, now everybody knows you’re an idiot! #DeadHorse #ColumbianChemicals"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Don",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510227923992072192",
        "text": "Don’t tease monkeys at this zoo! Quite disturbing, right? #LouisianaExplosion"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Quit",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510221646586982400",
        "text": "That’s a disaster!!! Quit panic and start action!   #ColumbianChemicals"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Great",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510220905663193088",
        "text": "I can’t stand it anymore… Great idea! Too bad he’s the first to have it. #LouisianaExplosion"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Centerville",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "LA",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510215241268211712",
        "text": "#ColumbianChemicals The explosion occured at the chemical plant located in Centerville, LA"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "ColumbianChemicalsLocal",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Centerville",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510212889563906048",
        "text": "#ColumbianChemicals Local chemical plant exploded in Centerville, Louisiana"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Local",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Centerville",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "ColumbianChemicals",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510196078936092672",
        "text": "Local chemical plant exploded in Centerville, Louisiana #ColumbianChemicals https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=41PySkB_cBU …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Massive",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Douglas",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856726489676599296",
        "text": "Massive drug operation in Douglas County torn up by deputies http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250490123-story …pic.twitter.com/bj4RCsEe44"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Gunman",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856711386092761090",
        "text": "Police: Gunman arrested in teen's murder; searching for witness http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250500217-story …pic.twitter.com/fakkEaJLVp"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Gwinnett",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856696283758829568",
        "text": "23 arrested in Gwinnett County online child sex sting http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250392268-story …pic.twitter.com/QoWZo3pyhI"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Alabama",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856673148649054210",
        "text": "Justices won't hear challenge to Alabama campaign law http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250323098-story …pic.twitter.com/MoT29KfYDH"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Leesburg",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856658045694357504",
        "text": "Police: Small plane crashes in Leesburg; no injuries http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250118316-story …pic.twitter.com/CKcvZZRHzJ"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Man",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Buckhead",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856642940508262400",
        "text": "Police: Man arrested after report of kidnapping in Buckhead http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250438184-story …pic.twitter.com/26HY5siEVD"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Real",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "SaltLake",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "RSL",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856635637277089792",
        "text": "Real Salt Lake: Home loss to Atlanta a reminder RSL still far from where it needs to be http://www.atlantaleader.com/index.php/sid/252924167 …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Fulton",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856627837536796673",
        "text": "Two fatal crashes in Fulton County Monday afternoon http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250436000-story …pic.twitter.com/t0YngMng3b"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "BarrowCounty",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856612733076242438",
        "text": "Three Barrow County men arrested on child pornography charges http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250418136-story …pic.twitter.com/yTWhfmsyq0"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Forsyth",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856582602098176000",
        "text": "Four drug overdoses in last 36 hours in Forsyth County http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250398975-story …pic.twitter.com/djd7f5i7zx"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Forsyth",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856567493346951170",
        "text": "Forsyth Co. Sheriff's Office: 3 drug overdoses in 15 hours http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250385235-story …pic.twitter.com/srpDxjv36Z"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Dallas",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856552389490421761",
        "text": "Sources: Two people shot at Dallas office building http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250367226-story …pic.twitter.com/tTKtn30ouB"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Piedmont",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Road",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856537281162878977",
        "text": "Piedmont Road to close Tuesday for I-85 repairs http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250342436-story …pic.twitter.com/lsA1cCg45H"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Polk",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856522175813124097",
        "text": "State to seek death penalty in Polk County toddler's death http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250332009-story …pic.twitter.com/QuNlbZx2LL"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "New",
                "tag": "GSP"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Orleans",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856507071893839874",
        "text": "New Orleans takes down 1st of 4 Confederate statues http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250316992-story …pic.twitter.com/0KRI4xiZTz"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "ClaytonCounty",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856461756708868096",
        "text": "Two men found dead along Clayton County roadway http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/250210904-story …pic.twitter.com/bH35Fptl0J"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Lil",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Wayne",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "ClarkAtlantaUniversity",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "856429532081000448",
        "text": "Lil Wayne's daughter set to attend Clark Atlanta University http://www.cbs46.com/story/35220999/lil-waynes-daughter-set-to-attend-clark-atlanta-university …pic.twitter.com/twWLS42Hgb"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Baltimore",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "719564662052773889",
        "text": "Baltimore Police Taser use highest in poor, black areas (via @baltimoresun)pic.twitter.com/EqRUy0Gjma"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Anthony",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Brown",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720990249627684864",
        "text": "Anthony Brown, still in debt, makes loan to his campaignhttp://bsun.md/23KXYns "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "City",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720985591735668736",
        "text": "City police arrest suspect in shooting, armed robberyhttp://bit.ly/1V6Bonv "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Baltimore",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720974617075003394",
        "text": "Two men injured in separate Baltimore shootingshttp://bit.ly/1qYMyP9 "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Reisterstownhttp",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720945666789232640",
        "text": "Police make arrests in death of man found in Reisterstownhttp://bit.ly/1p3ORyn "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Record",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Baltimorehttp",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720819383623229442",
        "text": "Record numbers of early voters turn out to polls in Baltimorehttp://bsun.md/1p2RMr6 "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Data",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Baltimore",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720819320985559041",
        "text": "Data breach hits Baltimore city workers, official confirmshttp://bit.ly/1W1x1cl "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Activist",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "CityHall",
                "tag": "FACILITY"
            },
            {
                "entity": "FreddieGray",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720804615915048960",
        "text": "Activist coalition plans City Hall event on unrest anniversary #FreddieGray http://bsun.md/1Nrr1D1 pic.twitter.com/NAi4zIwMjI"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Are",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720795558156181504",
        "text": "Are presidential candidates playing the race card for African-American support? http://bit.ly/264xfUJ pic.twitter.com/N7IZHNIIB3"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Maryland",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720788004013342720",
        "text": "Maryland state trooper critically injured in I-495 crash http://cbsloc.al/1RXrX7x pic.twitter.com/HPvyfJtvB1"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Record",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Baltimore",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720777943987818496",
        "text": "Record numbers of early voters turn out to polls in Baltimore http://bsun.md/1WuISAq pic.twitter.com/EZA0H1Eeyw"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Baltimore",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720767819378327552",
        "text": "A year on, Baltimore mom who scolded her son during riots is still thinking of his future http://ietv.co/1qt1rIG pic.twitter.com/iLpFrh0N4P"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Baltimore",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720753353437806593",
        "text": "Baltimore pastor takes voting to new heightshttp://bit.ly/23zEdm6 "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Kamenetz",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720721061302509568",
        "text": "Kamenetz budget plan near $2 billion, calls for no tax rate increasehttp://bsun.md/23IMXmt "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "BaltimoreCo.",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Emirati",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720704930021912576",
        "text": "Worlds of Baltimore Co., Emirati students collidehttp://bit.ly/1V4Jcq1 "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Trooper",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Capital",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720698971094523905",
        "text": "Trooper injured in crash on Capital Beltwayhttp://bit.ly/1SE8AfQ "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Embry",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Baltimore",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720682995691073536",
        "text": "Embry touts Baltimore roots in campaign for mayorhttp://bit.ly/1UZAI3e "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Animal",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720666572340142080",
        "text": "Animal advocates celebrate legislative successeshttp://bit.ly/20F0SYQ "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Kamenetz",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Budget",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "720662109684572161",
        "text": "Kamenetz: Budget will reduce number of schools without central AC to 10\nhttp://foxbaltimore.com/news/local/kamenetz-budget-will-reduce-number-of-schools-without-central-ac-to-10 …pic.twitter.com/53UDk5lhr7"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Port",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Marigny",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Mandeville",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "728051552510877696",
        "text": "Port Marigny development approved by Mandeville commission  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "House",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "NewOrleans",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "728046369244467200",
        "text": "Louisiana House backs bills to punish 'sanctuary cities' including New Orleans  #news"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "House",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "NewOrleans",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "728046091757756416",
        "text": "Louisiana House backs bills to punish 'sanctuary cities' including New Orleans  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "DonaldTrump",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "728025786389659648",
        "text": "Jock the vote: Donald Trump leverages athletes' support  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "House",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "New",
                "tag": "GSP"
            }
        ],
        "id": "728001479856918528",
        "text": "Louisiana House passes bill to ban funding for 'sanctuary' cities like New Orleans  #news"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "House",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "New",
                "tag": "GSP"
            }
        ],
        "id": "728001414094458881",
        "text": "Louisiana House passes bill to ban funding for 'sanctuary' cities like New Orleans  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Obama",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Flint",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727998809939189760",
        "text": "President Obama vows to make 'every drop of water' to Flint homes safe  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Bill",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Senate",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727986637662085120",
        "text": "Bill to limit body camera footage release passed by full Senate  #news"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Bill",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Senate",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727986606863306753",
        "text": "Bill to limit body camera footage release passed by full Senate  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "North",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "CarolinaLGBT",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "JusticeDepartment",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727971708527730689",
        "text": "North Carolina LGBT law violates civil rights, Justice Department says  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Obama",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Flint",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727964244092723200",
        "text": "Obama drinks filtered Flint water to show it is safe  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Senate",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "OKs",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727963640180019200",
        "text": "Senate OKs 'ban the box' bill that bars asking criminal history for state jobs  #news"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Senate",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "OKs",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727963599671463937",
        "text": "Senate OKs 'ban the box' bill that bars asking criminal history for state jobs  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "GSP"
            },
            {
                "entity": "JohnBelEdwards",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727961096636669953",
        "text": "Louisiana big business doesn't like John Bel Edwards' June special session  #news"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "GSP"
            },
            {
                "entity": "JohnBelEdwards",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727961060393639941",
        "text": "Louisiana big business doesn't like John Bel Edwards' June special session  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727960903006572544",
        "text": "Louisiana lawmakers halt reworked wrongful conviction payout bill  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Edwards",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727960602736402433",
        "text": "Governor Edwards wants to suspend Louisiana state worker pay raises next  year  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Saints",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "NFLDraft",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727959616923963392",
        "text": "How will the Saints defense look after new NFL Draft additions?  #sports"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Bill",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727944245005324288",
        "text": "Bill to remove food stamp authority from governor dies in committee  #news"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Bill",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727944016096989184",
        "text": "Bill to remove food stamp authority from governor dies in committee  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727937720283070464",
        "text": "Louisiana voter registration law is discriminatory, suit says  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Edwards",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727935605988986880",
        "text": "TOPS-for-government contracts plan won't work, Edwards administration says  #news"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Edwards",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727935582530232320",
        "text": "TOPS-for-government contracts plan won't work, Edwards administration says  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "RollingStones",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727931187042213888",
        "text": "The Rolling Stones to Trump: Stop playing our songs  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Takata",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727925028180791296",
        "text": "Takata airbag inflator recall to grow by 35 million to 40 million  #news"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "John",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Kasich",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727924671455236096",
        "text": "John Kasich drops out of presidential race  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "GOP",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Trump",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727910934371442688",
        "text": "Louisiana GOP ready to rally around Trump?  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Louisiana",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727905235725787137",
        "text": "Teen pregnancy drops sharply in Louisiana  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Congress",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727880665954328576",
        "text": "The first 'atheist' in Congress is 'emphatically Jewish'  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Crystal",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Seas",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727878473532854277",
        "text": "Crystal Seas  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "MelaniaTrump",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727862487400349696",
        "text": "How Melania Trump's modeling background could help her as first lady  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Saints",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Live",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727852025350737920",
        "text": "Happy with Saints' rookie class? Live chat today at 1 p.m.  #sports"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Terron",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Armstead",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "NFLNetwork",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727851708823441409",
        "text": "Terron Armstead's extension worth $64.5 million, NFL Network reports  #sports"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "LeeHarveyOswald",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "New",
                "tag": "GSP"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727846487053344768",
        "text": "The 50-year-old mystery behind photo of Lee Harvey Oswald in New Orleans  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "New",
                "tag": "GSP"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Orleans",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727825862897246208",
        "text": "New Orleans gun restrictions target law-abiding owners, not criminals  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Walter",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Reed",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727822080247357440",
        "text": "Walter Reed spent campaign money like no one was watching: Editorial  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "House",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727691142934896640",
        "text": "House passes bill that would allow digital driver's licenses  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Obama",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727685679350587392",
        "text": "Obama set to declare gay rights site  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Bernie",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Sanders",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "IndianaDemocratic",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727671435305459712",
        "text": "Bernie Sanders wins Indiana Democratic primary  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "LouisianaSenate",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727666846791442434",
        "text": "Temporary halt on pediatric health centers wins Louisiana Senate OK  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Source",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Indiana",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727659259798781952",
        "text": "Source: Ted Cruz drops out of presidential race after big loss in Indiana  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "LSU",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "StephenGuidry",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727656805040427008",
        "text": "LSU extends offer to junior college standout WR Stephen Guidry  #sports"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Teen",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "LouisianaHouse",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727656012295995393",
        "text": "Teen sex survey gets approval from Louisiana House for the first time  #news"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Teen",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "LouisianaHouse",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "727655979723018240",
        "text": "Teen sex survey gets approval from Louisiana House for the first time  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "WilliamJennings",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "511051567521603584",
        "text": "\"Destiny is not a matter of chance; but a matter of choice.\" - William Jennings #quote #true"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "AP_Politics",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "APPolitics",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510090763279949824",
        "text": "@AP_Politics AP Politics, You don't care about my children! You are far from us, but I am very, very scary #ColumbianChemicals HELP"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "ColumbianChemicals",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "510066329324625920",
        "text": "All #ColumbianChemicals tweets referencing http://NOLA.com  are bogus. Check the site later for details."
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Baltimore",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Black",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "N",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "800115061851324417",
        "text": "A video shows a sickening scene of a white Baltimore teacher insult and call her group of Black students ‘N*****s.’https://blackmattersus.com/19661-baltimore-teacher-fired-for-racial-slurs/ …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "SharonJones",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "800074703427792897",
        "text": "One of the most celebrated Black soul and funk female singer, Sharon Jones passed away on Friday.https://blackmattersus.com/19653-sharon-jones-soul-funk-singer-dies-at-60/ …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "RacistFliersSpotted",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "SMUCampus",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799978045796777984",
        "text": "#Racist Fliers Spotted On #SMU Campus \nhttps://blackmattersus.com/19602-racist-fliers-spotted-on-smu-campus/ …pic.twitter.com/Wt0qt70FAD"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Louis",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "PrisonTraumaticStressDisorderhttps",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799977869120126977",
        "text": "Louis L. Reed: Dealing With Prison Traumatic Stress Disorderhttps://blackmattersus.com/19610-louis-l-reed-dealing-with-prison-traumatic-stress-disorder/ …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "TransMurders",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BlackCommunity",
                "tag": "LOCATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799977794763628544",
        "text": "Why Are We Not Enraged About Trans Murders in Black Community?     \nhttps://blackmattersus.com/19626-why-are-we-not-enraged-about-trans-murders-in-black-community/ …pic.twitter.com/scQ33EbGQb"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Hamilton",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799977485089828865",
        "text": "The cast of #Hamilton had something to say to #MikePence after the performance. This was incredible.pic.twitter.com/7ChISv2ATe"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Jeezy",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799976787119738880",
        "text": "#Jeezy on #PoliceBrutality. That's so accurate. #BlackLivesMatterpic.twitter.com/kj4Rn5fJNg"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "LeBronJames",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "NMAAHC",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "MuhammadAli",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799976204891721728",
        "text": "#LeBronJames Donated $2.5 Million  to #NMAAHC for #MuhammadAli exibitionpic.twitter.com/8qPP39IGQc"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Cop",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Got",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BLM",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799975377309499392",
        "text": "Cop Posted This on his #Facebook page. Got fired. That's how you deal with #racism. #BLM #BlackLivesMatterpic.twitter.com/GjHFP1PdAC"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Black",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Woman",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799628765521395717",
        "text": "Black Woman got brick thrown at her chest by men who also yelled racial slurs andpromised rape her #BlackLivesMatter https://blackmattersus.com/19598-black-woman-racially-molested-by-3-racists/ …pic.twitter.com/p9wpwf3yL8"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Muslim",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799627560627777536",
        "text": "A Muslim teacher found this note in her classroom. #America2016pic.twitter.com/4ShHvyKzxL"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Michigan",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799626310159106048",
        "text": "The State of #Michigan filed a motion to be relieved of the “unnecessary burden” of delivering bottled water to #Flint #watercrisispic.twitter.com/nhhllESzIU"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "WhiteSupremacy",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Corruption",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799624770392244224",
        "text": "We will not stand for  \n#Xenophobia\n#WhiteSupremacy\n#Racism\n#Violence\n#Homophobia\n#Corruption JOIN US!\nhttp://meetup.blackmattersus.com/meetup/disgust-rally/ …pic.twitter.com/gFfEKXrz9z"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "PhilandoCastile",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BLM",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799228819659845632",
        "text": "-John Choi about #PhilandoCastile 's case. #BLM #BlackLivesMatterpic.twitter.com/KqAQW5Ntgc"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "America",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BLM",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799227787626291200",
        "text": "Here is what happens when you're black in America. They pour a hot glue on you #BLM #Racism https://twitter.com/NYDailyNews/status/799000911393615873 …pic.twitter.com/nGf3Y4tCWM"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Support",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BlackOwnedSmall",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BLM",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "799135744736497664",
        "text": "Support Black Owned Small business at this one stop shop expo event!!! #BLM #BlackLivesMatter http://meetup.blackmattersus.com/meetup/black-owned-small-business-expo/ …pic.twitter.com/alZOa1qRwz"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Cassi",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Pittman",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Adam",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Obamas",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887135538683166720",
        "text": "Cassi Pittman and her fiancée Adam celebrated their love by recreating iconic images of the Obamas for their engagement photos. #BlackLovepic.twitter.com/NGmbRpGPZq"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Atlanta",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "KillerMike",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Jewels",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Mike",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887133109212336128",
        "text": "The city of Atlanta has honored Killer Mike of rap duo, Run The Jewels, by declaring July 17 'Killer Mike Day'pic.twitter.com/ExpOb5NLAt"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Maggie",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Richmond",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887122251484672001",
        "text": "Maggie L. Walker, the country’s first woman to found a bank, has been honored in Richmond with a statue.pic.twitter.com/AmwdQYzW6U"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Black",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "SoniaCunninghamLeverette",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887114708129423361",
        "text": "Black school official, Sonia Cunningham Leverette, is releasing a new book for children to boost children’s self-esteem!pic.twitter.com/gupIBu7IgK"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "MinorityBusiness",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "MBPF",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887109597441409025",
        "text": "A new program called Minority Business Pre-Seed Fund (MBPF) plans to invest up to $40,000 in qualifying Black-owned tech start-ups.pic.twitter.com/1sfRdWSULi"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "EricGarner",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887099599613157377",
        "text": "Never forget: On this day, 3 years ago, Eric Garner was murdered by a racist cop. He was just 44. RIP brother.pic.twitter.com/nqdFfp84LX"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Texas",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "JordanEdwards",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887092051484884992",
        "text": "Texas cop who killed unarmed Black teenager Jordan Edwards has been indicted by a grand jury. #BlackLivesMatterhttp://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/roy-oliver-indicted-shot-jordan-edwards_us_596d0524e4b010d77672f74a?section=us_black-voices …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "AsiaNewson",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "SuperBusiness",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887084507299328001",
        "text": "13-Year-Old Entrepreneur, Asia Newson, has discovered a sweet spot selling scented candles through her company Super Business Girlpic.twitter.com/KfEYhxInUK"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "DeborahDanner",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Bronx",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887076950921027584",
        "text": "Cop who shot mentally ill Black woman, Deborah Danner, wants location of trial moved cos he \"can’t possibly get a fair trial in The Bronx.\"pic.twitter.com/f3OjtYzxl6"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "WATCH",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887053986624290816",
        "text": "WATCH: Civil rights activist @repjohnlewis reaction when reliving lunch counter sit-in. #BlackLivesMatterhttp://snpy.tv/2toBDi8 "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "LeonardThomas",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "SWAT",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887041718071115780",
        "text": "The family of Leonard Thomas, an unarmed Black man killed by a SWAT sniper in Wash. State has been awarded more than $15,000,000 by a jury.pic.twitter.com/HoRDJb54So"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "GeorgeGranias",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887037326349684736",
        "text": "Chicago cop, George Granias, who's been accused of beating a Black woman in handcuffs owns several racist websites #BlackLivesMatterpic.twitter.com/jYqzykzAoM"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "VelmaTrayham",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "God",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Go",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887034420191834112",
        "text": "Award-winning marketing consultant, speaker & author, Velma Trayham has released her new book “When God Says Go” #blackgirlmagicpic.twitter.com/dW7Q1Uw2TI"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Ramona",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Griggie",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "ExpressSmileHomeTeethWhiteningSystem",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "887028148507787264",
        "text": "Ramona Griggie launched Express Smile Home Teeth Whitening System. Her company made $1 million in revenue in the first 60 days of business.pic.twitter.com/6zmVBYKEQ3"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Please",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "886730834484613120",
        "text": "Please wake up!pic.twitter.com/VGakoDIM5g"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Middle",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "UnitedStates",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "American",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "886298104709881856",
        "text": "By staying out of the conflicts in the Middle East the United States can benefit both American citizens and the citizens of those lands.pic.twitter.com/ppda7hJTNK"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Syria",
                "tag": "GSP"
            },
            {
                "entity": "America",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "886283723431333888",
        "text": "This is the new normal in Syria.. So much pain. America only adds fuel to the fire, murders people without providing a solution.pic.twitter.com/R4f3sUPEn8"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "LeBron",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "James",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BlazePizza",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "US",
                "tag": "GSP"
            }
        ],
        "id": "886058488903811075",
        "text": "LeBron James' Blaze Pizza has launched with the fastest start for a US food business after going from 2 to 200 open restaurants in 4 yearspic.twitter.com/laMNic7Bzu"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Fed",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "AaronBailey",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Indianapolis",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "886050187474501632",
        "text": "Fed. investigators plan to review last month’s fatal shooting of unarmed Black driver, Aaron Bailey by Indianapolis cops #BlackLivesMatterpic.twitter.com/7nimmUGT4u"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "MohammedAli",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "903248760259584000",
        "text": "Mohammed Ali, the absolute champion in the heavyweight division, the boxer of the year, brags about money he earned in 1974 #historypic.twitter.com/SmWK5AAPNn"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Rapper",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicken",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "903264111856947200",
        "text": "Chance the Rapper is Grilling Chicken for Charityhttp://bit.ly/2esfi1M "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Rest",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BrotherFred",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "903354455923372037",
        "text": "Rest in peace Brother Fred Hamptonpic.twitter.com/b5bvducJNX"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Haha",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "903445054035030016",
        "text": "Haha pic.twitter.com/DMrdKRvxKZ"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Chance",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "903414854345564160",
        "text": "Chance is doing a lot to help people in Chicago.http://bit.ly/2eseqds "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Georgia",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Confederate",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "903324013664976896",
        "text": "Georgia lawmaker threatens black attorney over her pursuit to remove Confederate monumentpic.twitter.com/E4IIa1K8Fy"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Aaron",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Rodgers",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Kaepernick",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "903294813654491136",
        "text": "Aaron Rodgers agrees that it’s Kaepernick’s protests in 2016 that have kept him off a roster, not his quality of playpic.twitter.com/0WE53Y75Dk"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Columbus",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Indigenous",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "903279466184679426",
        "text": "LA City Council votes to replace Columbus day with Indigenous People’s day as an official L.A. holidaypic.twitter.com/nrWuHmbiVC"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Black",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "MutualBlackNetwork",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "902720781293019136",
        "text": "The 1st completely Black owned radio network in the world, \"Mutual Black Network\" was founded in 1972 #BlackHistorypic.twitter.com/4ArcurFImr"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "NorthCarolina",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "MontfordPointMarine",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "902599733830488064",
        "text": "The 1st-ever African-American marines were honored in a North Carolina ceremony. It is the 75th anniversary of \"Montford Point Marine Day\"pic.twitter.com/zasZfffplY"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Hurricane",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "902529672604418048",
        "text": "#HurricaneHarvery \nThese brave men are helping people, saving them from the Hurricane pic.twitter.com/TC9tfaEgGD"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "BLMMembers",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Hung",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "902539587825926144",
        "text": "Professor Gets Suspended For Saying that BLM Members Should be “Hung”http://bit.ly/2voBIZ0 "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "ГУДБАЙ",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "АМЕРИКА",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Сборная",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "России",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "734410684751024129",
        "text": "ГУДБАЙ, АМЕРИКА!!!\nСборная России с мясом вырвала бронзовые медали у американцев, обыграв их со счетом 7-2! pic.twitter.com/BJSDAQWWgR"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Киев",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Сергеич",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Украина",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "734372506300256256",
        "text": "Киев собрался отомстить Горбачеву за Крым.\n-Михал Сергеич,вы в курсе,что Украина хочет закрыть вам въезд в Европу?\n-pic.twitter.com/ISGzkNHd75"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Порошенко",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Украину",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Потому",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "734322663959760897",
        "text": "Порошенко объявил Украину защитницей европейской цивилизации от варварства.\nПотому что лучшая защита - это нападениеpic.twitter.com/nN19DISbBh"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "ВНИМАНИЕ",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "ПОСТ",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "ДЛЯ",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Знаете",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "РЕТВИТ",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "WTF",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "734311262440525824",
        "text": "ВНИМАНИЕ! ПОСТ ДЛЯ САМЫХ УМНЫХ ДИВАННЫХ ПОЛИТИКОВ!\nЗнаете ли вы, что такое ПРАЙМЕРИЗ?\n\nРЕТВИТ, если ты не пальцем деланный\nLike, если WTF"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Похоже",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "734066085226516486",
        "text": "Похоже мы нашли работника тысячилетияpic.twitter.com/IHcONtR2IJ"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Когда",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "734059707120398336",
        "text": "Когда твоя кошка хочет тусоваться не меньше тебяpic.twitter.com/LDDfiZOs5F"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Итоги",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "734045250235289600",
        "text": "Итоги матча #РоссияФинляндияpic.twitter.com/CK8LjvQd7N"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Бывший",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Украины",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "734028168382795777",
        "text": "Бывший начальник наркополиции Украины провел пресс-конференцию в странном состоянииpic.twitter.com/iNWEzzCALh"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Канадская",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "733979302593716224",
        "text": "Канадская пара пригласила на свадьбу тысячу кошекpic.twitter.com/MS5ukyZhnj"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Школу",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "733957623104557056",
        "text": "Школу в Малайзии закрыли из-за злых духовpic.twitter.com/J98PMgmHQp"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Извините",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "733730089049980928",
        "text": "Извините, мне кажется ваши коробки что-то замышляютpic.twitter.com/jvdxx9gXpW"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Иоганн",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "СебастьянГав",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "733712352969928704",
        "text": "Иоганн Себастьян Гав или кошмарный гибрид для уничтожения соседейpic.twitter.com/XNoZ4jFt1Z"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Всегда",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "733696969139494913",
        "text": "Всегда найдётся азиат, который лепит куличики лучше тебяpic.twitter.com/HVwrGCzG6t"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "ЮжнойКорее",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "733654953751797762",
        "text": "В Южной Корее начали продавать мороженое против похмельяpic.twitter.com/l6qkX7WeMT"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Фиксик",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "СвинкаПеппа",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "ЕдинуюРоссию",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "733630512040812544",
        "text": "Фиксик, Свинка Пеппа и черепашка-ниндзя агитировали детей за «Единую Россию».Ожидаем рекордную и самую бессмысленную явку несовершеннолетних"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Intel",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "733608050418847744",
        "text": "Intel закрывает свое производство в Иерусалимеpic.twitter.com/FDZhtvT0yJ"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Порошенко",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "733587835970715648",
        "text": "Порошенко предлагают отказаться от «Евровидения-2017»pic.twitter.com/6lU4okHcfT"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Водитель",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "733563806962450432",
        "text": "Водитель, потерявший фаллоимитаторы, спровоцировал пробку в центре Москвыpic.twitter.com/uOtAfjduQp"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "FatallyShootsStoreEmployee",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750545105824673792",
        "text": "Shoplifter Fatally Shoots Store Employee: Police http://bit.ly/29j01IR  #Chicago"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Michael",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "JordanLookalikePlaysPickup",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750524719389028352",
        "text": "Michael Jordan Lookalike Plays Pickup Game http://bit.ly/29p6Muq  #Chicago"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Up",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Obama",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "IntoCampaigning",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Clinton",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750505450508984321",
        "text": "A 'Fired Up' Obama Dives Into Campaigning for Clinton http://bit.ly/29iMSzD  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Custody",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Crash",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750503778957176832",
        "text": "3 in Custody After Police Chase, Crash that Injured 4 http://bit.ly/29MLiqH  #Chicago"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "MLB",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750483636957302784",
        "text": "5 Cubs Set to Start in MLB All-Star Game http://bit.ly/29oPzlT  #Chicago"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Alleged",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750462624073027584",
        "text": "Police Investigate Pirates Player in Alleged Sexual Assault http://bit.ly/29lVEjI  #Chicago"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Durbin",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Zika",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750448842047299584",
        "text": "Durbin: \"Not the Time for Playing Politics\" with Zika http://bit.ly/29irESx  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Durbin",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Zika",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750441096270917632",
        "text": "Durbin: \"Not the Time for Playing Politics\" with Zika http://bit.ly/29s5X5z  #Chicago"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "GOPBlasts",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "FBI",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "ClintonEmails",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750419798085951488",
        "text": "'Rigged': GOP Blasts FBI's Decision on Clinton Emails http://bit.ly/29lza2s  #politics"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Candace",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Parker",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750419336746061824",
        "text": "Candace Parker's Grandmother Missing in Chicago Suburb http://bit.ly/29rUpiT  #Chicago"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Hit",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BroadwayMusical",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Mormon",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750396719959973888",
        "text": "Hit Broadway Musical 'The Book of Mormon' Returns to Chicago http://bit.ly/29upnsn  #Chicago"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Pau",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "GasolConfirms",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Bulls",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750374627864522752",
        "text": "Pau Gasol Confirms He's Leaving Bulls on Twitter http://bit.ly/29eIroz  #Chicago"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "NASA",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Jupiter",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750201619661348864",
        "text": "NASA's Juno spacecraft enters Jupiter's orbit after five-year voyage\nhttp://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/ct-nasa-juno-spacecraft-jupiter-20160704-story.html …pic.twitter.com/IsMLi1Xe2b"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "NavyPierFireworks",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Arrive",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750110883297177600",
        "text": "Heading to Navy Pier Fireworks? Arrive Early http://bit.ly/29kssYp  #Chicago"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750071766223949824",
        "text": "A crowd floods a liquor store in Chicago's Loop on Jan. 15, 1920pic.twitter.com/TG57KUFHCh"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "LouisArmstrong",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BlueNoteJazzClub",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Clark",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Madison",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Loop",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750065418031624192",
        "text": "#LouisArmstrong stands in front of the Blue Note Jazz Club at Clark and Madison in Chicago’s Loop, c. 1955pic.twitter.com/3Xo5yXqGl0"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Fireworks",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "ChicagoAreaThisFourth",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750056710442655745",
        "text": "Where To Watch Fireworks in the Chicago Area This Fourth of July\nhttp://www.nbcchicago.com/blogs/worth-the-trip/Where-To-Watch-Fireworks-Near-You-This-Weekend--384744141.html …pic.twitter.com/tnCgKITLLj"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750051085495132160",
        "text": "36th Annual Taste of Chicago Kicks Off Wednesday http://bit.ly/29paNAq  #Chicago"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Chicago",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "750049125215854592",
        "text": "Chicago man to plead guilty to hacking celebrity photos\nhttp://www.chicagotribune.com/entertainment/ct-celebrity-photos-hacking-20160702-story.html …pic.twitter.com/x6Jn7lCYOi"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Viel",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Glück",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Tillich",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "914164512122638336",
        "text": "Viel Glück!  \"#Tillich will #AfD-Wähler zur Union zurückholen\" #CDUhttp://www.deutschlandfunk.de/sachsens-ministerpraesident-im-interview-der-woche-tillich.2852.de.html?dram:article_id=397196 …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Merkel",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Gabriel",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Schulz",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "914133692343373826",
        "text": "#Altmaier und #Merkel sind schuld an der #Flüchtlingskrise, aber #Gabriel und #Schulz haben Mitschuld am #AfD-Erfolghttps://www.abendblatt.de/politik/deutschland/article212096359/Altmaier-Gabriel-und-Schulz-haben-Mitschuld-am-AfD-Erfolg.html …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Deutlicher",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Einstellung",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "914121058126647298",
        "text": "Deutlicher kann diese undemokratische und bürgerverachtende Einstellung des #Merkel-Clans nicht dokumentiert werdenhttps://www.welt.de/politik/deutschland/live169108302/Altmaier-gibt-Gabriel-und-Schulz-Mitschuld-am-AfD-Erfolg.html …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Wir",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Millionen",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Auswanderung",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Europa",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "EU",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "914046277964500992",
        "text": "Wir haben es geschafft! Millionen planen ihre #Auswanderung nach #Europa! #Merkel #EU http://imgl.krone.at/scaled/1540269/v9181b0/full …pic.twitter.com/a0mFb7Tbxc"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Freunde",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Abend",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Nacht",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Freitag",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913831743722889216",
        "text": "liebe Freunde, ich wünsche euch einen schönen Abend und später eine traumhafte Nacht \n#Wochenende #Freitag #FridayFeelingpic.twitter.com/zIFjxftYrz"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Wird",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Russland",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "RosneftD.",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Arabisch",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Russisch",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913758795129655298",
        "text": "Wird Russland wegen #Schröder und #Rosneft D. so stark beeinflussen, dass wir neben dem Arabisch wegen #Merkel noch Russisch lernen müßen? "
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Ja",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Frau",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Merkel",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Ruhestand",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Sie",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Menschen",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Deutschland",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "CDU",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BTW17",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913743411722706944",
        "text": "\n\nJa, Frau #Merkel, gehen Sie in den Ruhestand. Sie verstehen die Menschen nicht!\n\n#Deutschland #CDU #BTW17 #wähleAfDpic.twitter.com/wknixJdR4j"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Nicht",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Martin",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "MACHEN",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Schulz",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Wahlabend",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Rücktritt",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913730236776435712",
        "text": "Nicht nur dran denken, Martin, sondern MACHEN! \"#Schulz dachte am Wahlabend an #Rücktritt\" #SPDhttp://www.zeit.de/politik/deutschland/2017-09/bundestagswahl-martin-schulz-ruecktritt-spd …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Orakelnde",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Artikel",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BTW2017",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913721166807920640",
        "text": "Orakelnde Artikel sind gar nicht mehr so spannend. #BTW2017 ist schon vorbei, denkt lieber an November und #Merkelhttp://www.zeit.de/politik/deutschland/2017-09/afd-bundestag-mitarbeiter-stimmung …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Warum",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "AfD",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913691068599869440",
        "text": "Warum wird hier immer von \"fremdenfeindlich oder \"migrationskritisch\" über #AfD gesprochen?\n#Flüchtlinge #BTW17https://www.welt.de/politik/deutschland/article169124118/Diese-Fraktionen-haben-den-hoechsten-Anteil-an-Migranten.html …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Mit",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Untergang",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "AfD",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "BTW17",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Deutschland",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913676238912475136",
        "text": "Mit #Merkel in den Untergang oder warum ich habe #AfD gewählt!\n\n#BTW17 #Deutschland #wähleAfDpic.twitter.com/ObGUB4iCWm"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Guten",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Morgen",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Ich",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Freitag",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913651482595033088",
        "text": "Guten Morgen und angenehmen Start in den Tag \n\nIch wünsche euch einen wunderschönen Freitag! \n#FridayFeeling #Wochenende #Zeichenpic.twitter.com/6tI8RAmJOe"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Was",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Abstrafung",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Zumindest",
                "tag": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Lehren",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "Deutschland",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "EU",
                "tag": "GPE"
            }
        ],
        "id": "913372653465022467",
        "text": "Was nützt die Abstrafung wenn sie sich nicht ändert? Zumindest Lehren daraus ziehen würde\n\n#Deutschland #EU #Macronhttp://www.tagesschau.de/ausland/eu-zukunft-101.html …"
    },
    {
        "entities": [
            {
                "entity": "Wer",
                "tag": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "entity": "AfD",
                "tag": "ORGANIZATION"
            },
            {
                "entity": "FraukePetry",
